RG 073, Department of Veterans' Affairs
Connecticut State Library
Department of Veterans' Affairs records
1866-1990
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. Dept. of Veterans' Affairs
256.5 cubic feet
The Department of Veterans' Affairs assists the State's veterans in obtaining benefits or privileges entitled to them under state and federal law. This record group includes records of the Fitch's Home for Soldiers and the Veterans Home and Hospital in Rocky Hill.
RG073
Multiple
Historical Note
The General Assembly created the Department of Veterans' Affairs in 1987 to assist the State's nearly 400,000 veterans in obtaining benefits or privileges entitled to them under state and federal law. In its first year, the Department of Veterans' Affairs had only one division, the Office of Advocacy and Assistance. In July 1988, the Veterans Home and Hospital in Rocky Hill merged with the Department, making the department's new mission to provide comprehensive health, social and rehabilitative services to all resident veterans in Connecticut. Today the agency consists of the Office of the Commission, the Office of Advocacy and Assistance, and the Veterans Home and Hospital (VHH).
While the Department of Veterans' Affairs conducts a wide variety of services, the State Archives only has those records relating to the Veterans' Home and Hospital (VHH) and its predecessor, Fitch's Home for Soldiers. While the majority of records in the State Archives were created before the establishment of the Department of Veterans' Affairs, it seemed logical to keep of the Veterans' Home materials together in this record group.
Fitch's Home for Soldiers and Orphans (1863 - 1940), also known as the Noroton Home, located in Darien, Connecticut, was first erected by private means for Soldiers and the children of Soldiers and was dedicated July 4, 1864. It was incorporated by an Act of Connecticut Legislation in 1874 and until 1883 receiving limited aid from the State of Connecticut. In 1887 the State assumed control and it was thereafter known as the Fitch's Home for Soldiers, deriving its name from the original founder Benjamin Fitch.
At the Fitch's Home, many of the State's Civil War Veterans were cared for as well as the Veterans of the Spanish American War and the World War I. Due to its limited facilities and the increase of returning veterans, the Veterans Home and Hospital Commission sought to relocate the Home. The new Veterans Home and Hospital was opened in Rocky Hill on August 28, 1940.
The Veterans Home and Hospital (1940 - present) was established for treatment and rehabilitation of Connecticut Veterans who served in or with the Armed Forces of the United States of America in time of war. The Hospital, which is accredited by the Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals, has a capacity of 350 beds. Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation is available with Physical Therapy, Recreational Therapy, Occupational Therapy, Speech Therapy and Audiology. Clinics include, but are not limited to, Cardiac, Dental, Diabetic, Orthopedic, Podiatry, Psychiatry, and Respiratory. A separate building, Fellowship House, is a long-term residence for recovering alcoholics. A 14 day program for substance abusers was opened in 1988.
Eligible veterans must have served during one of the following: Spanish American War; Philippine Insurrection; Moro Province; Boxer Rebellion; Cuban Pacification; Nicaraguan Campaign; Haitian Campaign; Mexican Border Service; World War I; World War II; Korean Campaign; Vietnam; Lebanon; Grenada; Operation Ernest Will; Panama Invasion; Operation Desert Shield and Operation Desert Storm.
See also the.
Scope and Content
Records generated by both Fitch's Home for Soldiers and the Veterans Home and Hospital are organized in six separate series.
Series 1. Patient Files (1930-1962) contain two types of records, traditional patient files that contain medical information and correspondence relating to the individual patient, and administrative files that contain application forms and death notices.
Series 2. Deceased Veterans Discharge Files (1882-1936) consist of approximately 2300 files of veterans who died while cared for at Fitch's Home for Soldiers. Although the veterans listed served primarily in the Civil War, a few Spanish American veterans may be included. The files are arranged by file number. The folders contain the veteran's name, unit, and town of residence, date of admission and pension certificate number. Other information, if known, include death date, burial information, and pension payments to the Home. A majority of the folders contain an admission permit and a signed receipt for personal effects. A limited number of files also include correspondence, personal history information, discharge papers, application forms, and other records concerning the veteran. Veteran name access is available by using the, a listing of which is available at the History and Genealogy reference desk.
Series 3. Administrative Files (1886-1990) contain records generated by the hospitals in the course of providing medical services to Connecticut veterans. They include records of the Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, the Hospital Commandant, financial records, personnel files, and maintenance reports.
Series 4. Death Records (1884-1971) are record books, maintained by both Fitch's and the Veterans Home, listing the name of the person who died and the date. No volumes exist between 1928 and 1950.
Series 5. Historical Subject Files (1866-1990) were created by the staff of the Veterans Home and Hospital to assist them with research into the institutions past and to document present day events. All original order was lost. The materials, grouped loosely by subject, include newspaper clippings, photographs, publications and subject files on a variety of topics.
Series 6. Miscellaneous Records (1878-1951), despite being limited in number, contain interesting and invaluable information. Although mostly related to Fitch's Home, there are also records here pertaining to New Haven Hospital, Hartford Hospital, and the Connecticut State Soldiers' Home. Included are records of invalid soldiers, necrological records, and historical rosters, as well as a superb collection of photos of Fitch's Home. The dates of these records span from 1878 to 1951, exhibiting a large and varied epoch in the history of Connecticut soldiers. These materials were removed from a larger accession due to their historic value.
Arrangement
Arranged in six series: Series 1. Patient Files, 1930-1962; Series 2. Deceased Veterans Discharge Files, 1882-1936; Series 3. Administrative Files, 1886-1990; Series 4. Death Records, 1884-1971; Series 5. Historical Subject Files, 1866-1990; and Series 6. Miscellaneous Records, 1878-1951.
Related Material
Researchers interested in either the Veterans' Home and Hospital (Rocky Hill) or its predecessor Fitch's Home for Soldiers should also check:
RG 002, General Assembly
RG 013, Military Department
Researchers interest in tracing individual veterans should consult:
RG 012, Connecticut State Library, War Records Department
RG 013, Military Department
Other sources of information include:
RG 049, Veterans Advisory Commission, 1943-1949
RG 052, Civil War Centennial Commission, 1959-1965
RG 081, Department of Connecticut United Spanish War Veterans, 1898-1972
RG 109, Military Order of Foreign Wars, 1901-1921
RG 113, Grand Army of the Republic, Connecticut Department, 1866-1956
RG 114, Sons of Union Veterans of the Civil War, 1909-1915
RG 118, Hartford City Guard Veteran Association, 1861-1917
RG 119, Army-Navy Club of Connecticut, 1892-1936
RG 122, Owen Machine Gun Veterans Association, 1920-1970
RG 124, Hartford City Guard, 1861-1917
RG 173, Military Service Veterans Organizations, 1885-1948. An artificial record group, the records are composed of those of Company K, Veterans Corps, First Infantry, Connecticut National Guard, and the Veterans Soldiers Association.
The Classified Archives card catalog also contains information on Connecticut's veterans.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. Dept. of Veterans' Affairs; Fitch's Home for the Soldiers; Veterans' Home and Hospital (Rocky Hill, Conn.)
Subjects:
Connecticut. Dept. of Veterans' Affairs -- Records and correspondence; Fitch's Home for the Soldiers -- Records and correspondence; Long-term care facilities -- Connecticut; Soldiers' homes -- Connecticut; Veterans' Home and Hospital (Rocky Hill, Conn.) -- Records and correspondence; Veterans' hospitals -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Clippings; Correspondence; Minutes; Pamphlets; Photographs; Reports
Restrictions on Access
Some of these records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
Patient records are protected under Connecticut General Statute 17a-548 and 19a-550. Only the patient or his/her immediate family can access the records. Please contact the State Archives staff to discuss access procedures. Some materials may be partially restricted (i.e. medical records mixed with general correspondence). In these cases, a member of the State Archives staff will remove all protected material before the researcher can access it. As a result, the material will not be available on a same day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
When the Veterans' Home and Hospital (VHH) opened its doors, many records created and maintained by its predecessor, Fitch's Home for Soldiers, were transferred to VHH. Eventually, VHH transferred their records, and materials they received from Fitch's, to the State Archives. Since the records were created, or maintained, by the Veterans' Home and Hospital, the State Archives has not divided the material into separate record groups or series. Researchers, however, must remember two important dates. The first, Veterans Home and Hospital opened and Fitch's closed in August 1940. Fitch's Home created any records created prior to that date; Veterans Home and Hospital, Rocky Hill created anything after. Second, VHH merged with the Department of Veterans Affairs in 1988. At that time, the Commissioner of Veterans' Affairs assumed the statutory powers and duties formerly vested in the Veterans Home and Hospital Commission. An appointed six member Board of Trustees advises the commissioner on policy and operation matters at VHH.
Container List
- Series 1. Patient Files, 1927-1962
  All patient files are restricted.
  - Fitch's Home for Soldiers
    - Case files, 1927-1931; 1 cubic foot; 1987-041B
      Arranged alphabetically by patient name.
    - Deceased Soldiers Cards, 1932-1935; 1 cubic foot; 1992-067
      Arranged chronologically by year.
  - Veterans' Home and Hospital
    - 1935-1956, 107 cubic feet; 1989-007
      Arranged by patient file number.
    - 1930-1939, 11 cubic feet; 1992-116
    - Discharges, 1940-1941; 1 cubic foot; 1996-066
    - 1936-1939, 2 cubic feet; 2000-009
    - Adjutant's Department, 1942-1962; 39 cubic feet; 2000-021
- Series 2. Deceased Veterans Discharge Files, 1882-1936; 1993-032
  Veteran name access is available by using the, a listing of which is available at the History and Genealogy reference desk.
  - File number 4 - 413 (Box 1)
  - File number 414 - 777 (Box 2)
  - File number 778 - 1052 (Box 3)
  - File number 1053 - 1309 (Box 4)
  - File number 1310 - 1515 (Box 5)
  - File number 1516 - 1712 (Box 6)
  - File number 1714 - 1929 (Box 7)
  - File number 1933 - 2195 (Box 8)
  - File number 2196 - 2401 (Box 9)
  - File number 2422 - 2620 (Box 10)
  - File number 2623 - 2840 (Box 11)
  - File number 2842 - 3089 (Box 12)
  - File number 3090 - 3335 (Box 13)
  - File number 3339 - 3523 (Box 14)
  - File number 3524 - 3700 (Box 15)
- Series 3. Administrative Files, 1886-1990
  - 1992-021 (part)
    - Fitch's Home for Soldiers and Veterans Home and Hospital (Rocky Hill), 1927-1990
      Items in Box 26 were incorporated into Box 25.
      - Accreditation, 1949-1986 (Box F-1)
      - Activation of Ward 2C Hospital (Box F-1)
      - Administration, Correspondence, 1942-1976 (Box F-1)
      - Admissions, Policy, General Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box F-1)
      - Addresses, Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1960-1987 (Box F-2)
      - Commissioners (Box F-2)
        - Frances T. Bower, M.D. (Box F-2)
        - Robert R. Cherlin (Box F-2)
        - Joseph Cermak (Box F-2)
        - Francis J. Drag (Box F-2)
        - Leonard Goodie (Box F-2)
        - William Johnston (Box F-2)
        - Joseph Leonard (Box F-2)
        - Frank Mongillo, M.D. (Box F-2)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, Commissioners (Box F-2)
        - Sally Ann McDuffie (Box F-2)
        - Terence McNulty, M.D. (Box F-2)
        - Serge G. Miholy (Box F-2)
        - Louis E. Molinary (Box F-2)
        - H. Richard Newell, Jr. (Box F-2)
        - William J. Pomfret, Chairman (Box F-2)
        - Dominic J. Romano (Box F-2)
        - Michael D. Santonrasso (Box F-2)
        - Quinn (Box F-2)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission Chairman, 1927 (Box F-2)
      - Commissioners Data (Box F-2)
        - Subcommittee Audit Reports, 1987 (Box F-2)
      - Finance Subcommittee Meetings, 1986 (Box F-2)
      - Commissioner, John L. Levitow (Box F-2)
      - Admission Policy, General Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box F-3)
      - Admission Approvals, 1979-1986 (Box F-3)
      - Admission Disapproval, 1986-1988 (Box F-3)
      - Admission Policy, General Correspondence, 1959-1967 (Box F-3)
      - Affirmative Action, Officer, 1980-1983 (Box F-3)
      - Affirmative Action, Correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box F-3)
      - Affirmative Action, Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box F-4)
      - Affirmative Action, General Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box F-4)
      - Affirmative Action, Guidelines (Proposed), 1984 (Box F-4)
      - Affirmative Action, Status, 1980 (Box F-4)
      - Affirmative Action, Monthly Reports, 1984 (Box F-4)
      - Affirmative Action, Recruitment, 1981-1982 (Box F-4)
      - Agency Police, 1981-1983 (Box F-4)
      - Agency Police, M. Seiler Incident (Box F-4)
      - Alcoholism Committee Meetings, 1971-1973 (Box F-4)
      - American Federation of Labor, CIO (Box F-4)
      - American Legion Auxiliary, 1966-1985 (Box F-4)
      - Agendas (Box F-5)
        - Finance Subcommittee, 1986 (Box F-5)
        - Audit Reports, 1987 (Box F-5)
        - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1960-1979 (Box F-5)
        - ByLaws, 1955-1981 (Box F-5)
        - Commission Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box F-5)
        - General Orders, 1953-1992 (Box F-5)
        - ByLaws, Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1982-1987 (Box F-5)
        - Special Orders, 1978-1986 (Box F-5)
      - Anesthetist, 1949-1983 (Box F-6)
      - Anesthetic Services, 1955-1975 (Box F-6)
      - Annex, 1950-1958 (Box F-6)
      - Assistant Hospital, Executive Officer (Box F-6)
      - Attorney General, Correspondence, 1940-1982 (Box F-6)
      - Audits, 1953-1964 (Box F-6)
      - Auditors of Public Accounts (Box F-6)
      - Barracks, 1959-1978 (Box F-6)
      - Auditors, 1965-1972 (Box F-6)
      - Budget, 1933-1951 (Box F-7)
      - Ledger, Fitch’s Home, 1932-1943 (Box F-7)
      - Hospital Activities, 1936-1938 (Box F-7)
      - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box F-8)
      - Building Services, 1953-1987 (Box F-8)
      - Burial and Headstones, 1959-1985 (Box F-8)
      - Burial Park Foundation, 1984 (Box F-8)
      - Cemetery, Evergreen, New Haven (Box F-8)
      - Census, 1980-1985 (Box F-8)
      - Chaplain, Catholic, 1977-1979 (Box F-8)
      - Chapel and Services Catholic, 1940, 1957-1960 (Box F-8)
      - Chaplain Protestant, 1959, 1971-1978 (Box F-8)
      - Chaplain Jewish, 1947-1987 (Box F-8)
      - Chief of Medicine, 1969-1973 (Box F-8)
      - Civil Defense Bulletins, Transportation, Warden, Welfare (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense, 1954 (Box F-9)
      - Filing, Administration Building (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense Bulletins, Education, Emergency Finance, Fire Service, General, Ground Observer Corps, Policy (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense Press Releases (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense, Allocation of Space, National Emergency (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense Bulletins (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense, 1951 (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense, General Correspondence, 1941 (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense, All local directories, Bomb reconnaissance (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense Pamphlets (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense Training (Box F-9)
      - Civil Defense Statewide Civil Defense Test (Box F-9)
      - Chief of Medicine, 1974-1976 (Box F-10)
      - Chief of Medicine, Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box F-10)
      - Chief of Medicine, Professional Services (Box F-10)
      - Chief of Staff, 1955-1979 (Box F-10)
      - Christmas Menus, 1977-1983 (Box F-10)
      - CIAI General, Historical (Box F-10)
      - CHRO, 1967-1980 (Box F-10)
      - CIAI Rehabilitation and Physical Medicine (Box F-10)
      - Cigarettes, 1968-1980 (Box F-10)
      - Civil Defense, Veterans Home and Hospital, 1957-1969 (Box F-10)
      - Commandant, Institution Award, 1985-1987 (Box F-10)
      - Chotkowski, Ludmil A., M.D. Personnel (Box F-11)
        - Work resume, 1973-1974 (Box F-11)
        - Travel Request, 1989-1990 (Box F-11)
        - Tuberculosis (Box F-11)
        - Projects, Emergency Repair Pumps, Elevator Repairs, Nurses Stations, Nurses Call Station, Aluminum Siding Building 19, Install Water Mains, Window Replacement Administration Building, Repaint Building, Aluminum Siding (Box F-11)
      - Commissary, Misc. (Box F-12)
      - Commissary, Hospital and Health Care, 1969-1985 (Box F-12)
      - Community Service Restitution Program (Box F-12)
      - Commitment, 1957-1977 (Box F-12)
      - Connecticut Hospital Association, 1988-1989 (Box F-12)
      - Conservators Accounts, 1979-1983 (Box F-12)
      - Contracts, 1985-1987 (Box F-12)
      - Cooks, Ernest Jr. Colonel (Box F-12)
      - Cost per capita, Veterans Home and Hospital, Finance Officer (Box F-12)
      - Cottages Tally Sheets, 1973-1976 (Box F-12)
      - Court, Disciplinary Regulations (Box F-12)
      - Data Processing, 1986-1988 (Box F-12)
      - Deeds and Insurance Policies (Box F-13)
      - Deputy Commandant (Box F-13)
      - Directives, 1966-1976 (Box F-13)
      - Disabled American Veterans, 1985-1986 (Box F-13)
      - Disaster Plans, 1977-1982 (Box F-13)
      - Discharge Commission Policies, 1972-1979 (Box F-13)
      - Education Committee (Box F-13)
      - Energy Action (Box F-13)
      - Emergency Conservation (Box F-13)
      - Etherington Commission, 1973-1979 (Box F-13)
      - Executive Community Meeting, 1970-1979 (Box F-13)
        - Professional Staff, 1958-1969 (Box F-13)
      - Executive Office Home Position (Box F-13)
      - Farm (Box F-13)
      - Feasibility Study, Niantic (Box F-14)
      - Filler Report (Box F-14)
      - Estate Collections, 1989-1990 (Box F-14)
      - Estate Collections, 1988-1989 (Box F-15)
      - Fund, Veterans Gifts, 1971-1972 (Box F-15)
      - Estates, General Correspondence, 1960-1975 (Box F-15)
      - Estate Collections, 1985-1987 (Box F-16)
      - Estate Collections, 1986-1987 (Box F-17)
      - Estate Collections, Closed out, 1987-1988 (Box F-17)
      - Estate Collections, 1983-1989 (Box F-18)
      - Estate Collections, 1982-1984 (Box F-19)
      - Estate Collections, 1980-1982 (Box F-20)
      - Estates, General Correspondence, 1981 (Box F-20)
      - Estates, General Correspondence and Medical Payments, 1982 (Box F-20)
      - Estate Collections, 1976-1981 (Box F-21)
      - Estates, General Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box F-21)
      - Estates Collections, 1969-1976 (Box F-22)
      - Fall Carnival (Box F-23)
      - SUS Correspondence, Monthly Reports, 1982-1989 (Box F-23)
      - War Dates, 1948-1977 (Box F-23)
      - Weekly Bulletin, 1974-1978 (Box F-23)
      - Women’s Relief Corps (Box F-23)
      - Weights and Measures (Box F-23)
      - Patient Care, Meeting Minutes, 1953-1958 (Box F-23)
      - Commandants Report, 1964-1971 (Box F-23)
      - Federal Grants (Box F-24)
      - Federal Inspections, 1935 (Box F-24)
      - Finance Correspondence (Box F-24)
      - Finance and Control, 1958-1978 (Box F-24)
      - Finance Officer, Correspondence, 1953-1973 (Box F-24)
      - Fire Prevention, Fire Safety and Inspection (Box F-24)
      - Fire Reports, 1974-1983 (Box F-24)
      - Fire Prevention, 1965-1979 (Box F-24)
      - Fire Alarm System, 1940-1976 (Box F-24)
      - Food Services, 1955-1985 (Box F-24)
      - Foxhole, 1978-1985 (Box F-25)
      - Fund, Activity Expenditures, 1957-1987 (Box F-25)
      - Fund, Activity Monthly Reports, 1984-1989 (Box F-25)
      - Fund, IGW (SCV 4-96 and SCV 4-57) (Box F-25)
      - Fund, IGWF, 1980-1985 (Box F-25)
      - Fund Contributors, 1989 (Box F-27)
      - Fund, IGWF, Monthly Reports, 1981-1989 (Box F-27)
      - Fund, Individual Residents Deposits, 1953-1958 (Box F-27)
      - Fund, IGWF Contributors, 1981-1982 (Box F-28)
      - Fund Contributors, 1983-1988 (Box F-28)
      - Fund, IGW, Accounts, Purchases, 1962-1982 (Box F-29)
      - Fund, Purchases, 1983 (Box F-30)
      - Fund, IGWF Purchases, 1983-1989 (Box F-30)
      - Fund, Fitch and Post Humous (Box F-30)
      - Fund, IGWF Accounts, 1953-1983 (Box F-30)
      - Fund, Service Contact (Box F-30)
      - Fusco, Colonel, Asst. Commandant (Box F-31)
      - Geraci, Lucian A., M.D. Senior Physician (Box F-31)
      - Governor Dempsey Correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box F-31)
      - Greenhouse, Removal of (Box F-31)
      - Hartford Electric Light Co (Box F-31)
      - Headstones, 1951, 1960, 1972 (Box F-31)
      - Health Department, 1976-1982 (Box F-31)
      - Health Services, Veterans Home employees, 1959-1979 (Box F-31)
      - Hospital Abbreviated Reports, 1975 (Box F-31)
      - Hospital Activities Reports, 1978-1983 (Box F-31)
      - Hospital Consulting Staff, Former Members (A-H) (Box F-31)
      - Hospital Consulting Staff, Former Members (I-Z) (Box F-31A)
      - Hospital, General Correspondence, 1936-1979 (Box F-31A)
      - Howley, Robert Colonel, Commandant (Box F-31A)
      - Housing, on grounds, 1966-1983 (Box F-31A)
      - Housing, on grounds, 1984-1987 (Box F-32)
      - Housing, waiting list, 1980-1987 (Box F-32)
      - Householders, VHH Regulations, 1957-1979 (Box F-32)
      - Infection Control, 1959-1984 (Box F-32)
      - Internships, 1932-1972 (Box F-32)
      - July 4th Celebrations, 1980-1981 (Box F-32)
      - Laboratory, 1945-1979 (Box F-32)
      - Laundry Services, 1960-1979 (Box F-33)
      - Laws affecting Veterans and their Dependents, 1965-1977 (Box F-33)
      - Legislation, Federal, 1961-1974 (Box F-33)
      - Proposed Legislation, School Site (Box F-33)
      - Legislation, 1945-1980 (Box F-33)
      - Legislation, 1933 (Box F-34)
      - Minutes, Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1947-1958 (Box F-34)
        Includes reports, notes on legislation, and photographs.
      - Legislation, 1975-1976 (Box F-35)
      - Legislation, Staff, 1973-1987 (Box F-35)
      - Library, Veterans Home and Hospital, 1966-1975 (Box F-35)
      - Loyalty Day (Box F-35)
      - Maintenance, State, 1959-1986 (Box F-36)
        Includes reports on maintenance concerns including security.
      - Meal tickets (Box F-37)
      - Medicare, 1966-1980 (Box F-37)
      - Mess operations (Box F-37)
      - Memos (Box F-37)
      - Medical, School Approved, 1972 (Box F-37)
      - Medical Staff, Conference Academic (Box F-37)
      - Medical Staff, General, 1939-1989 (Box F-37)
      - Meetings, Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1959-1973 (Box F-38)
      - Meetings, Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, 1985-1987 (Box F-39)
      - Minutes, Patient Care and Rehabilitation, 1961-1962 (Box F-40)
      - Patient Care Index, 1953-1958 (Box F-40)
      - Veterans Home and Hospital Commission, Correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box F-40)
      - Planning Extended Care Unit Project, 1967-1972 (Box F-40)